(Sheldon:)among background noise.
(Bernadette:)Mine has a fully developed
(Bernadette:)immune system.
(Sheldon:)Ours doesn't need
(Sheldon:)an immune system
because it lives
(Sheldon:)in a state-of-the-art
German incubator.
(Amy:)Sheldon, that's enough.
Oh, yeah, no, fine.
(Sheldon:)Let's just agree
that both creations
(Sheldon:)are special in their own way
(Sheldon:)and it is foolish
to try and compare them.
(Sheldon:)Although, we didn't need
to have sex with Howard
(Sheldon:)for ours, so we win.
(Raj:)This is fun.
(Raj:)I have never cleaned
a toilet before.
(Isabella:)You're kidding.
(Raj:)No, I grew up with a house
full of servants
(Raj:)and now I have
a cleaning lady...
(Raj:)...who is a lovely woman
(Raj:)who I have great respect for.
(Isabella:)It's okay, you're allowed
to have a cleaning lady.
(Raj:)Oh, good, because
she also walks my dog,
(Raj:)buys my groceries
and cuts my hair.
(Isabella:)I think that's called a mommy.
(Cleaner:)Uh...
(Raj:)So, forgive me...
(Raj:)forgive me for being nosy,
but is-is there a wedding ring